[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Machine Learning Concepts",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You should have at least ______ times as many data points as the total number of features",
      "answers": [
        "10",
        "20",
        "5",
        "2"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["10"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of these represents data where we already know what the target attribute is",
      "answers": [
        "labeled data",
        "unlabeled data",
        "formatted data",
        "unformatted data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["labeled data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of these represents data that has been collected with no target attribute",
      "answers": [
        "labeled data",
        "unlabeled data",
        "formatted data",
        "unformatted data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["unlabeled data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which of these are synonyms of the concept of a feature",
      "answers": [
        "attribute",
        "column",
        "training data",
        "testing data",
        "row",
        "observation",
        "sample"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["attribute",
        "column"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Which of these are synonyms of the concept of an observation",
      "answers": [
        "attribute",
        "column",
        "training data",
        "testing data",
        "row",
        "data point",
        "sample"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["row",
        "data point",
        "sample"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Has a defined schema, the schema is the information needed to interpret the data, including attribute names and their assigned data types",
      "answers": [
        "structured data",
        "unstructured data",
        "semi-structured data",
        "testing data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["structured data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Has no defined schema or structural properties. Makes up majority of data collected",
      "answers": [
        "structured data",
        "unstructured data",
        "semi-structured data",
        "testing data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["unstructured data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "It is too unstructured for relational data, but has some organizational structure. Usually in the form of CSV, JSON, or XML",
      "answers": [
        "structured data",
        "unstructured data",
        "semi-structured data",
        "testing data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["semi-structured data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "It usually has some pre-processing done before data is loaded into it",
      "answers": [
        "data warehouse",
        "data lake",
        "relational database",
        "no sql database"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["data warehouse"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Processing done on import (schema-on-write)",
      "answers": [
        "data warehouse",
        "data lake",
        "relational database",
        "no sql database"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["data warehouse"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Data classified, stored with user in mind",
      "answers": [
        "data warehouse",
        "data lake",
        "relational database",
        "no sql database"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["data warehouse"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Ready to be used with BI tools (query and analysis)",
      "answers": [
        "data warehouse",
        "data lake",
        "relational database",
        "no sql database"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["data warehouse"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "No pre-processing before data is loaded into it",
      "answers": [
        "data warehouse",
        "data lake",
        "relational database",
        "no sql database"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["data lake"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Processing done on export (schema-on-read)",
      "answers": [
        "data warehouse",
        "data lake",
        "relational database",
        "no sql database"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["data lake"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Many different sources and formats",
      "answers": [
        "data warehouse",
        "data lake",
        "relational database",
        "no sql database"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["data lake"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Raw data may not be ready for use",
      "answers": [
        "data warehouse",
        "data lake",
        "relational database",
        "no sql database"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["data lake"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Raw data may not be ready for use",
      "answers": [
        "data warehouse",
        "data lake",
        "relational database",
        "no sql database"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["data lake"]
    }
  }
]